<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edit Sticky Notes on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/edit-sticky-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Edit Sticky Notes on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/edit-sticky-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Format Text: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Copy Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Cut Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Paste Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Format Text With Click Method 1: First edit a sticky note and select any text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note How to Edit Text in a Sticky Note How to Select Text in a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Mouse With Keyboard With Keyboard Shortcut How to Delete Text in a Sticky Note No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;See a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note Step 1: First open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note: With Click With Right Click With Search With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note With Click Method 1: First open the Notes List. Go to the upper left corner and click the &amp;ldquo;New note&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; button. A new sticky note appears. Method 2: Open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
