<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation Guides on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/installation-guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation Guides on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/installation-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Install GIMP on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-gimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-gimp/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is GIMP? How to Download GIMP With Google Chrome How to Download GIMP With Firefox How to Install GIMP With Shortcut How to Install GIMP Without Shortcut How to Install GIMP From the Microsoft Store With Browser How to Install GIMP From the Microsoft Store How to Open GIMP With Shortcut How to Open GIMP Without Shortcut How to Pin GIMP to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin GIMP to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin GIMP to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin GIMP to Start How to Uninstall GIMP No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Scribus on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-scribus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-scribus/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Scribus? How to Download Scribus With Google Chrome How to Download Scribus With Firefox How to Install Scribus How to Open Scribus With Shortcut How to Open Scribus With Search How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Scribus to Start How to Uninstall Scribus No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Inkscape? How to Download Inkscape With the Google Chrome Browser How to Download Inkscape With the Firefox Browser How to Install Inkscape How to Install Inkscape From the Microsoft Store How to Open Inkscape How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Inkscape to Start How to Uninstall Inkscape No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
