<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Whiteboard on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/microsoft-whiteboard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft Whiteboard on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/microsoft-whiteboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Insert Objects in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-insert-objects-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-insert-objects-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change an Ink Object to a Shape: With Click With Keyboard How to Insert a Sticky Note: With Click With Right Click From a Note Grid How to Insert a Note Grid How to Insert a Reaction: With Click Into a Sticky Note How to Insert Text: With Click With Right Click How to Insert Shapes How to Undo: With Click With Keyboard How to Redo: With Click With Keyboard No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use the Eraser and Highlighter in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-eraser-highlighter-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-eraser-highlighter-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Select the Eraser: With Click With Keyboard How to Change Eraser Width How to Change Eraser Stroke: How to Erase Entire Stroke How to Erase Partial Stroke How to Select the Highlighter: With Click With Keyboard How to Change Highlighter Width How to Change Highlighter Color: To Default Colors To Custom Colors No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;See a video tutorial:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Ink Objects in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-ink-objects-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-ink-objects-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Switch to Inking Mode: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Insert an Ink Object How to Switch the Pen: How to Switch to the First Pen With Click How to Switch to the First Pen With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Second Pen With Click How to Switch to the Second Pen With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Third Pen With Click How to Switch to the Third Pen With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Single Arrow Tip With Click How to Switch to the Single Arrow Tip With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Double Arrow Tip With Click How to Switch to the Double Arrow Tip With Keyboard Shortcut How to Draw Straight Lines: With Ruler With Keyboard With Touch Screen How to Change Pen Width How to Change Pen Opacity: By Default With Menu How to Change Pen Color: To Default Colors To Custom Colors No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Microsoft Whiteboard App Display (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-the-whiteboard-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-the-whiteboard-display/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pan Across the Canvas: With Click With Keyboard How to Change the Whiteboard Color How to Change the Whiteboard Background How to Enhance Inked Shapes No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Pan Across the Canvas With Mouse Step 1: First open a whiteboard template. Click, hold, and drag the mouse in any direction to pan across the canvas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Zoom In and Out of the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-zoom-in-and-out-of-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-zoom-in-and-out-of-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Zoom In: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut With Menu With Fit to Screen How to Center to Selection How to Zoom Out: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut With Menu With Fit to Screen No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Zoom In With Click Step 1: First open a whiteboard template. In the lower right side click the &amp;ldquo;Zoom in &amp;quot; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Customize the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-customize-microsoft-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-customize-microsoft-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize Whiteboard: With Click With Menu With Keyboard How to Maximize Whiteboard: With Click With Double Click With Menu With Keyboard How to Restore Whiteboard: With Click With Double Click With Menu With Keyboard How to Resize Whiteboard: With Mouse With Menu With Keyboard How to Move Whiteboard: With Mouse With Menu With Keyboard No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;See a tutorial video:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Print Settings in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-print-settings-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-print-settings-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change Printing Orientation: With Print Window With System Dialog With Printing Preferences How to Change Color Settings: With Print Window With System Dialog With Printing Preferences How to Change Paper Size How to Change Printing Scale How to Change Pages per Sheet How to Change Margins How to Add or Remove the Header and Footer How to Add or Remove Background Graphics How to Change Page Order How to Change Paper Source How to Change Media No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Print in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-print-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-print-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Print in Whiteboard: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Close the Print Window: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut With Close How to Specify Pages: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Print on Both Sides: With Print Window With Printing Preferences How to Add a Printer: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Change the Printer: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Let Whiteboard Change Printing Preferences No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Manage Whiteboards in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-manage-whiteboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-manage-whiteboards/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Rename a Whiteboard: With Menu With &amp;ldquo;More Options&amp;rdquo; How to Share a Whiteboard How to Export a Whiteboard: As an Image As a PDF As a Zip File How to Navigate the Whiteboard Downloads Window: How to Open the Downloads Window How to Close the Downloads Window How to Search the Downloads Window How to Clear All History in the Downloads Window How to Open the Computer Downloads Folder How to Report a Whiteboard No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Delete a Whiteboard How to Close Microsoft Whiteboard: With Click With Right Click With Hover Witih Hover and Right Click With Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Delete a Whiteboard Step 1: First open a whiteboard. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;My whiteboards&amp;rdquo; or house button. Step 2: Hover over a whiteboard and click the &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open Content in Microsoft Whiteboard (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-content-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-content-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open Images How to Open PDFs How to Open the Timer How to Open the Ruler: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open the Source Code How to Open the &amp;ldquo;Find&amp;rdquo; Window No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open Images Step 1: First open a whiteboard. On the bottom toolbar click the &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard To the Taskbar: With Search With Right Click From Start How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;whiteboard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-microsoft-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-microsoft-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Microsoft Whiteboard? How to Open Microsoft Whiteboard With Search How to Open a Blank Whiteboard: With Click With Close By Default How to Open a Whiteboard Template: With the Templates Window With Preview With Menu How to Refresh a Whiteboard No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Microsoft Whiteboard? As a cloud-based or online app, Microsoft Whiteboard enables multiple users to collaborate on digital whiteboards in real time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
