<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;See a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window. Step 2: After the cursor becomes a double sided arrow, click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Inkscape? How to Download Inkscape With the Google Chrome Browser How to Download Inkscape With the Firefox Browser How to Install Inkscape How to Install Inkscape From the Microsoft Store How to Open Inkscape How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Inkscape to Start How to Uninstall Inkscape No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List: With Search With Hover With Right Click From a Sticky Note With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start menu that opens, click in the search bar at the top and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Hover With Right Click From the Notes List No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note with Double Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. In the Notes List window, double click a sticky note to open it. How to Open a Sticky Note With Hover Step 1: Open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin the Sticky Notes App: To the Taskbar With Search To the Taskbar With Right Click To the Taskbar From Start To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Sticky Notes to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video here:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? Sticky Notes is a note-taking app that comes with Windows 11. Notes can have formatted text (bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, and bulleted lists), images, and recognized URLs. For further customization, choose from seven different colors of sticky notes and a &amp;ldquo;Dark&amp;rdquo; mode for the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Notepad? How to Open Notepad With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Notepad? Notepad is a basic text editor that comes with Windows 11. This app creates text files for various applications, such as editing code or writing stories. Notepad can save files with UTF-8 encoding, and customize document headers and footers with special codes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
