<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Undo: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Redo: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Undo With Right Click Step 1: First edit a sticky note. Right click anywhere in the note. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Undo&amp;rdquo;. The previous action is reversed. How to Undo With Keyboard Shortcut Step 1: Edit a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Format Text: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Copy Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Cut Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Paste Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Format Text With Click Method 1: First edit a sticky note and select any text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note How to Edit Text in a Sticky Note How to Select Text in a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Mouse With Keyboard With Keyboard Shortcut How to Delete Text in a Sticky Note No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;See a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note Step 1: First open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note: With Click With Right Click With Search With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note With Click Method 1: First open the Notes List. Go to the upper left corner and click the &amp;ldquo;New note&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; button. A new sticky note appears. Method 2: Open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Scribus on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-scribus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-scribus/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Scribus? How to Download Scribus With Google Chrome How to Download Scribus With Firefox How to Install Scribus How to Open Scribus With Shortcut How to Open Scribus With Search How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Scribus to Start How to Uninstall Scribus No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Close the Notes List and Sticky Notes With Right Click How to Close the Notes List: With Click With Hover With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts How to Close a Sticky Note: With Click With Hover With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Close the Notes List and Sticky Notes With Right Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Theme Color of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-change-sticky-notes-theme-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-change-sticky-notes-theme-color/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Sticky Notes App Theme Color: With Start With the Notes List With Right Click No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Change the Sticky Notes App Theme Color With Start Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Mouse How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. At the top of the window, click, hold, and drag to move the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Show All Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-show-all-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-show-all-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Show All Notes: With Right Click With Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Show All Notes With Right Click Step 1: First minimize or hide all notes. Go down to the taskbar and right click the Sticky Notes app icon. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Show all notes&amp;rdquo;. The Notes List and all sticky notes display on the Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Restore the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Restore the Notes List: With Double Click With Menu How to Restore a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Restore the Notes List With Double Click Step 1: First maximize the Notes List. Double click the top of the maximized Notes List. The Notes List is restored to its original size before being maximized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Maximize the Notes List: With Menu With Double Click How to Maximize a Sticky Note: With Menu With Double Click No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Maximize the Notes List With Menu Step 1: First open the Notes List. Go down to the taskbar and hover the mouse over the Sticky Notes app icon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Minimize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize a Sticky Note: With Click From the Notes List From the Notes List With Right Click With Menu How to Minimize the Notes List: With Click With Menu With Right Click With Start With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Minimize a Sticky Note With Click Step 1: First open the Notes List and open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;See a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window. Step 2: After the cursor becomes a double sided arrow, click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Inkscape? How to Download Inkscape With the Google Chrome Browser How to Download Inkscape With the Firefox Browser How to Install Inkscape How to Install Inkscape From the Microsoft Store How to Open Inkscape How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Inkscape to Start How to Uninstall Inkscape No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List: With Search With Hover With Right Click From a Sticky Note With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start menu that opens, click in the search bar at the top and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Hover With Right Click From the Notes List No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note with Double Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. In the Notes List window, double click a sticky note to open it. How to Open a Sticky Note With Hover Step 1: Open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin the Sticky Notes App: To the Taskbar With Search To the Taskbar With Right Click To the Taskbar From Start To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Sticky Notes to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video here:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? Sticky Notes is a note-taking app that comes with Windows 11. Notes can have formatted text (bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, and bulleted lists), images, and recognized URLs. For further customization, choose from seven different colors of sticky notes and a &amp;ldquo;Dark&amp;rdquo; mode for the app.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
