<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customize Notepad on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/customize-notepad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customize Notepad on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/customize-notepad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Move the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Move Notepad: With Mouse With Right Click With Menu With a Tab How to Move a Tab: Outside a Window Into a Window No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Move Notepad With Mouse Step 1: First open Notepad. At the top of the window, click, hold, and drag the mouse to move the window. Release the mouse to stop moving the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Restore the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Restore Notepad: With Click With Double Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Restore Notepad With Click Step 1: First maximize Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Maximize&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window is restored to its original size. How to Restore Notepad With Double Click Step 1: Maximize Notepad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Maximize Notepad: With Click With Double Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a video:&#xA;How to Maximize Notepad With Click Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Maximize&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window maximizes. How to Maximize Notepad With Double Click Step 1: Open Notepad. Double click the top of the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Minimize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize Notepad: With Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Minimize Notepad With Click Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Minimize&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;-&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window minimizes. How to Minimize Notepad With Right Click Step 1: Open Notepad. Right click either the top or the upper left corner of the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize Notepad: With Mouse With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Resize Notepad With Mouse Step 1: First open Notepad. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window, until the cursor becomes a double sided arrow. Step 2: Click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window. Release the mouse to stop resizing the window.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
