<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Whiteboard on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/open-whiteboard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Whiteboard on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/open-whiteboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Delete a Whiteboard How to Close Microsoft Whiteboard: With Click With Right Click With Hover Witih Hover and Right Click With Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Delete a Whiteboard Step 1: First open a whiteboard. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;My whiteboards&amp;rdquo; or house button. Step 2: Hover over a whiteboard and click the &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open Content in Microsoft Whiteboard (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-content-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-content-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open Images How to Open PDFs How to Open the Timer How to Open the Ruler: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open the Source Code How to Open the &amp;ldquo;Find&amp;rdquo; Window No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open Images Step 1: First open a whiteboard. On the bottom toolbar click the &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard To the Taskbar: With Search With Right Click From Start How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;whiteboard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-microsoft-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-microsoft-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Microsoft Whiteboard? How to Open Microsoft Whiteboard With Search How to Open a Blank Whiteboard: With Click With Close By Default How to Open a Whiteboard Template: With the Templates Window With Preview With Menu How to Refresh a Whiteboard No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Microsoft Whiteboard? As a cloud-based or online app, Microsoft Whiteboard enables multiple users to collaborate on digital whiteboards in real time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
