<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notepad on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/notepad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notepad on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/notepad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Move the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Move Notepad: With Mouse With Right Click With Menu With a Tab How to Move a Tab: Outside a Window Into a Window No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Move Notepad With Mouse Step 1: First open Notepad. At the top of the window, click, hold, and drag the mouse to move the window. Release the mouse to stop moving the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Restore the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Restore Notepad: With Click With Double Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Restore Notepad With Click Step 1: First maximize Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Maximize&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window is restored to its original size. How to Restore Notepad With Double Click Step 1: Maximize Notepad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Maximize Notepad: With Click With Double Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a video:&#xA;How to Maximize Notepad With Click Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Maximize&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window maximizes. How to Maximize Notepad With Double Click Step 1: Open Notepad. Double click the top of the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Minimize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize Notepad: With Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Minimize Notepad With Click Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Minimize&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;-&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window minimizes. How to Minimize Notepad With Right Click Step 1: Open Notepad. Right click either the top or the upper left corner of the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize Notepad: With Mouse With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Resize Notepad With Mouse Step 1: First open Notepad. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window, until the cursor becomes a double sided arrow. Step 2: Click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window. Release the mouse to stop resizing the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Close a Window: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts With Click With Right Click With Double Click With Hover With Hover and Right Click With Right Click on Taskbar How to Close All Windows With Menu How to Close a Tab: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut With Click With Right Click How to Close Tabs: On the Right Side Multiple Tabs No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-files-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-files-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a File: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open a Window: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open a Tab: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut With Click With Right Click No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a File With Menu Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper left and click &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin Notepad to the Taskbar: With Search With Right Click From Start How to Pin Notepad to Start No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Notepad to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;notepad&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Notepad? How to Open Notepad With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Notepad? Notepad is a basic text editor that comes with Windows 11. This app creates text files for various applications, such as editing code or writing stories. Notepad can save files with UTF-8 encoding, and customize document headers and footers with special codes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
