<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edit Notepad on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/edit-notepad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Edit Notepad on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/edit-notepad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Display of the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-notepad-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-notepad-display/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Font: With Menu With Settings How to Change the Reading Order How to Insert Unicode Control Characters How to Show Unicode Control Characters How to Apply Reconversion No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Change the Font With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Navigate the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Use &amp;ldquo;Go To&amp;rdquo;: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Clear the &amp;ldquo;Go To&amp;rdquo; Window How to Exit the &amp;ldquo;Go To&amp;rdquo; Window: With Click With Keyboard No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Use &#34;Go To&#34; With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Go to&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Search for Text in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-search-text-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-search-text-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Use Find: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Use Find Next: With Menu With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Use Find Previous: With Menu With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Apply Match Case How to Apply Wrap Around How to Clear the Find Bar How to Exit the Find Window: With Click With Keyboard How to Use Find and Replace: With Menu With Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Undo: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Redo With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Undo With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Undo&amp;rdquo;. Notepad reverses the last action. How to Undo With Right Click Step 1: Edit a Notepad file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-files-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-files-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Edit Text in Notepad How to Select Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Copy Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Cut Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Paste Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Delete Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
