<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Close a Window: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts With Click With Right Click With Double Click With Hover With Hover and Right Click With Right Click on Taskbar How to Close All Windows With Menu How to Close a Tab: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut With Click With Right Click How to Close Tabs: On the Right Side Multiple Tabs No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-files-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-files-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a File: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open a Window: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open a Tab: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut With Click With Right Click No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a File With Menu Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper left and click &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin Notepad to the Taskbar: With Search With Right Click From Start How to Pin Notepad to Start No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Notepad to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;notepad&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Notepad? How to Open Notepad With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Notepad? Notepad is a basic text editor that comes with Windows 11. This app creates text files for various applications, such as editing code or writing stories. Notepad can save files with UTF-8 encoding, and customize document headers and footers with special codes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install GIMP on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-gimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-gimp/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is GIMP? How to Download GIMP With Google Chrome How to Download GIMP With Firefox How to Install GIMP With Shortcut How to Install GIMP Without Shortcut How to Install GIMP From the Microsoft Store With Browser How to Install GIMP From the Microsoft Store How to Open GIMP With Shortcut How to Open GIMP Without Shortcut How to Pin GIMP to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin GIMP to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin GIMP to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin GIMP to Start How to Uninstall GIMP No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Navigate the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Settings (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Switch Between Windows How to Cycle Forward Through All Windows How to Cycle Backwards Through All Windows How to Search For Sticky Notes How to Search for a Sticky Note Witih Click How to Clear the Search Bar How to Exit the Search Bar With Click How to Search for a Sticky Note With Keyboard Shortcut How to Clear the Search Bar With Keyboard Shortcut How to Move to a Word How to Move One Word to the Left How to Move One Word to the Right How to Move to the Start of a Line How to Move to the End of a Line How to Move to the Start of a Sticky Note How to Move to the End of a Sticky Note How to Move and Delete Words How to Delete the Previous Word How to Delete the Next Word No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Settings (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-sticky-notes-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-sticky-notes-settings/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Enable Insights in a Sticky Note How to Turn &amp;ldquo;Confirm Before Deleting&amp;rdquo; Off: With Settings With Click No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial: See it in action with this video:&#xA;How to Enable Insights in a Sticky Note Step 1: First open the Notes List. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; or gear button. Step 2: In the Settings window that opens, click under the &amp;ldquo;Enable Insights&amp;rdquo; section to toggle this option on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Delete Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-delete-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-delete-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Delete a Sticky Note: With Menu With Click From the Notes List With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Delete a Sticky Note With Menu Step 1: First open a sticky note. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Menu&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Delete note&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Images in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-images-in-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-images-in-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Add an Image to a Sticky Note How to View an Image in a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Right Click How to Navigate the Image Viewer Window: How to Resize the Image Viewer Window How to Maximize and Restore the Image Viewer Window How to Close the Image Viewer Window How to Save an Image: With Menu With Right Click How to Open an Image in Photos How to Edit the Description of an Image How to Remove the Description of an Image How to Delete an Image: With Menu With Right Click No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Undo: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Redo: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Undo With Right Click Step 1: First edit a sticky note. Right click anywhere in the note. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Undo&amp;rdquo;. The previous action is reversed. How to Undo With Keyboard Shortcut Step 1: Edit a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Format Text: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Copy Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Cut Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Paste Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Format Text With Click Method 1: First edit a sticky note and select any text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note How to Edit Text in a Sticky Note How to Select Text in a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Mouse With Keyboard With Keyboard Shortcut How to Delete Text in a Sticky Note No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;See a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note Step 1: First open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note: With Click With Right Click With Search With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note With Click Method 1: First open the Notes List. Go to the upper left corner and click the &amp;ldquo;New note&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; button. A new sticky note appears. Method 2: Open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Scribus on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-scribus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-scribus/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Scribus? How to Download Scribus With Google Chrome How to Download Scribus With Firefox How to Install Scribus How to Open Scribus With Shortcut How to Open Scribus With Search How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Scribus to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Scribus to Start How to Uninstall Scribus No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Close the Notes List and Sticky Notes With Right Click How to Close the Notes List: With Click With Hover With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts How to Close a Sticky Note: With Click With Hover With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Close the Notes List and Sticky Notes With Right Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Theme Color of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-change-sticky-notes-theme-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-change-sticky-notes-theme-color/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Sticky Notes App Theme Color: With Start With the Notes List With Right Click No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Change the Sticky Notes App Theme Color With Start Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Mouse How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. At the top of the window, click, hold, and drag to move the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Show All Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-show-all-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-show-all-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Show All Notes: With Right Click With Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Show All Notes With Right Click Step 1: First minimize or hide all notes. Go down to the taskbar and right click the Sticky Notes app icon. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Show all notes&amp;rdquo;. The Notes List and all sticky notes display on the Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Restore the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Restore the Notes List: With Double Click With Menu How to Restore a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Restore the Notes List With Double Click Step 1: First maximize the Notes List. Double click the top of the maximized Notes List. The Notes List is restored to its original size before being maximized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Maximize the Notes List: With Menu With Double Click How to Maximize a Sticky Note: With Menu With Double Click No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Maximize the Notes List With Menu Step 1: First open the Notes List. Go down to the taskbar and hover the mouse over the Sticky Notes app icon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Minimize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize a Sticky Note: With Click From the Notes List From the Notes List With Right Click With Menu How to Minimize the Notes List: With Click With Menu With Right Click With Start With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Minimize a Sticky Note With Click Step 1: First open the Notes List and open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;See a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window. Step 2: After the cursor becomes a double sided arrow, click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-install-inkscape/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Inkscape? How to Download Inkscape With the Google Chrome Browser How to Download Inkscape With the Firefox Browser How to Install Inkscape How to Install Inkscape From the Microsoft Store How to Open Inkscape How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Search How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar With Right Click How to Pin Inkscape to the Taskbar From Start How to Pin Inkscape to Start How to Uninstall Inkscape No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List: With Search With Hover With Right Click From a Sticky Note With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start menu that opens, click in the search bar at the top and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Hover With Right Click From the Notes List No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note with Double Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. In the Notes List window, double click a sticky note to open it. How to Open a Sticky Note With Hover Step 1: Open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin the Sticky Notes App: To the Taskbar With Search To the Taskbar With Right Click To the Taskbar From Start To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Sticky Notes to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video here:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? Sticky Notes is a note-taking app that comes with Windows 11. Notes can have formatted text (bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, and bulleted lists), images, and recognized URLs. For further customization, choose from seven different colors of sticky notes and a &amp;ldquo;Dark&amp;rdquo; mode for the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pdfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pdfs/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of all the PDF tutorials I created.&#xA;Installation Guides How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11 How to Install Scribus on Windows 11 How to Install GIMP on Windows 11 Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Customize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Minimize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Maximize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Restore the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Show All Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Move the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Change the Theme Color of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Close the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Images in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Delete Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit the Settings of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Navigate the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Navigate the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) How to Open Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/slides/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of all the Google Slides tutorials I created.&#xA;For full screen mode: Click the &amp;ldquo;Menu&amp;rdquo; or three vertical dots button. In the menu click &amp;ldquo;Enter Full Screen&amp;rdquo;. The keyboard shortcut for full screen mode is Ctrl + Shift + F.&#xA;Press Esc to exit full screen mode.&#xA;Installation Guides How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11 How to Install Scribus on Windows 11 How to Install GIMP on Windows 11 Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Customize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Minimize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Maximize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Restore the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Show All Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Move the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Window (Windows 11) How to Change the Theme Color of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Close the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Images in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Delete Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit the Settings of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/videos/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of all my YouTube video tutorials, created with kdenlive.&#xA;Installation Guides How to Install Inkscape on Windows 11 How to Install Scribus on Windows 11 How to Install GIMP on Windows 11 Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Customize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Minimize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Maximize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Restore the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Show All Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Move the Microsoft Sticky Note App Window (Windows 11) How to Change the Theme Color of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Close the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit Images in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Delete Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Edit the Settings of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Navigate the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Navigate the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) How to Open Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Ink Objects in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-ink-objects-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-ink-objects-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Switch to Inking Mode: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Insert an Ink Object How to Switch the Pen: How to Switch to the First Pen With Click How to Switch to the First Pen With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Second Pen With Click How to Switch to the Second Pen With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Third Pen With Click How to Switch to the Third Pen With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Single Arrow Tip With Click How to Switch to the Single Arrow Tip With Keyboard Shortcut How to Switch to the Double Arrow Tip With Click How to Switch to the Double Arrow Tip With Keyboard Shortcut How to Draw Straight Lines: With Ruler With Keyboard With Touch Screen How to Change Pen Width How to Change Pen Opacity: By Default With Menu How to Change Pen Color: To Default Colors To Custom Colors No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.&#xA;Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:&#xA;https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.&#xA;No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html&#xA;Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.&#xA;This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js&#xA;Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
