<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/slides/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of all the Google Slides tutorials I created.&#xA;For full screen mode:&#xA;Click the &amp;ldquo;Menu&amp;rdquo; or three vertical dots button. In the menu click &amp;ldquo;Enter Full Screen&amp;rdquo;. The keyboard shortcut for full screen mode is Ctrl + Shift + F.&#xA;Press Esc to exit full screen mode.&#xA;Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Microsoft Windows Clock App (Windows 11) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pdfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pdfs/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of all the PDF tutorials I created.&#xA;Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Microsoft Windows Clock App (Windows 11) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/openastickynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/openastickynote/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Hover With Right Click From the Notes List No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note with Double Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. In the Notes List window, double click a sticky note to open it. How to Open a Sticky Note With Hover Step 1: Open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pinstickynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pinstickynotes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin the Sticky Notes App: To the Taskbar With Search To the Taskbar With Right Click To the Taskbar From Start To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Sticky Notes to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram Bot for  GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tg-gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tg-gh/</guid>
      <description>Telegram Telegram is a cloud-based mobile and desktop messaging app with a focus on security and speed. It is free to use and extensively hackable. It also has a good bot support system. The API is also easy to implement and has many wrappers for building bots with the API.&#xA;GitHub Actions GitHub Actions is a CI/CD runtime for your GitHub repository. You can run almost anything from scripts to docker containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheese</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video here:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? Sticky Notes is a note-taking app that comes with Windows 11. Notes can have formatted text (bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, and bulleted lists), images, and recognized URLs. For further customization, choose from seven different colors of sticky notes and a &amp;ldquo;Dark&amp;rdquo; mode for the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/openstickynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/openstickynotes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video here:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? Sticky Notes is a note-taking app that comes with Windows 11. Notes can have formatted text (bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, and bulleted lists), images, and recognized URLs. For further customization, choose from seven different colors of sticky notes and a &amp;ldquo;Dark&amp;rdquo; mode for the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Traveling Ultralight</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-4/</guid>
      <description>I’m on a trip at the moment, and a friend who generously let me sleep on his couch looked at my small travel backpack and commented on how little I travel with: “That’s impressive,” he said.&#xA;I was a little surprised, because though I’ve gotten that comment before, it’s become normal for me to travel with just a small bag (10 lbs. or less, usually), and I have friends who travel with even less.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.&#xA;Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:&#xA;https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/videos/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of all my YouTube video tutorials, created with kdenlive.&#xA;Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Tutorials How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11) Microsoft Windows Clock App (Windows 11) Link to playlists here Normal Normal Normal Normal </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to test dark mode?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-7/</guid>
      <description>Here is how you can setup dark mode for Ink and test on various OS like iOS, Android, macOS and Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.&#xA;Heading 1 Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo shortcodes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-6/</guid>
      <description>Images Dave Herring Dave Herring Github Gist Youtube video Tweet Vimeo Instagram View this post on Instagram Callouts 💡 I guess this works </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Learned to Stop Procrastinating, &amp; Love Letting Go</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>The end of procrastination is the art of letting go.&#xA;I’ve been a lifelong procrastinator, at least until recent years. I would put things off until deadline, because I knew I could come through. I came through on tests after cramming last minute, I turned articles in at the deadline after waiting until the last hour, I got things done.&#xA;Until I didn’t. It turns out procrastinating caused me to miss deadlines, over and over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearlessness: How to Stop Running from Space</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>We spend our days filling in every available space, cramming in more tasks, responding to messages, checking social media and online sites, watching videos.&#xA;We are afraid of empty space in our lives.&#xA;The result is often a continual busyness, constant distraction and avoidance, lack of focus, lack of satisfaction with our lives.&#xA;We run from silence. We run from the spaces between tasks and appointments. We run from solitude and stillness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.&#xA;No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html&#xA;Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.&#xA;This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js&#xA;Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
