<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 11 on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/windows-11/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows 11 on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/windows-11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Print Settings in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-print-settings-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-print-settings-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change Printing Orientation: With Print Window With System Dialog With Printing Preferences How to Change Color Settings: With Print Window With System Dialog With Printing Preferences How to Change Paper Size How to Change Printing Scale How to Change Pages per Sheet How to Change Margins How to Add or Remove the Header and Footer How to Add or Remove Background Graphics How to Change Page Order How to Change Paper Source How to Change Media No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Print in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-print-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-print-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Print in Whiteboard: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Close the Print Window: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut With Close How to Specify Pages: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Print on Both Sides: With Print Window With Printing Preferences How to Add a Printer: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Change the Printer: With Print Window With System Dialog How to Let Whiteboard Change Printing Preferences No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Manage Whiteboards in the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-manage-whiteboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-manage-whiteboards/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Rename a Whiteboard: With Menu With &amp;ldquo;More Options&amp;rdquo; How to Share a Whiteboard How to Export a Whiteboard: As an Image As a PDF As a Zip File How to Navigate the Whiteboard Downloads Window: How to Open the Downloads Window How to Close the Downloads Window How to Search the Downloads Window How to Clear All History in the Downloads Window How to Open the Computer Downloads Folder How to Report a Whiteboard No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Delete a Whiteboard How to Close Microsoft Whiteboard: With Click With Right Click With Hover Witih Hover and Right Click With Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Delete a Whiteboard Step 1: First open a whiteboard. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;My whiteboards&amp;rdquo; or house button. Step 2: Hover over a whiteboard and click the &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open Content in Microsoft Whiteboard (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-content-in-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-content-in-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open Images How to Open PDFs How to Open the Timer How to Open the Ruler: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open the Source Code How to Open the &amp;ldquo;Find&amp;rdquo; Window No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open Images Step 1: First open a whiteboard. On the bottom toolbar click the &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard To the Taskbar: With Search With Right Click From Start How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Microsoft Whiteboard to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;whiteboard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-microsoft-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-microsoft-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Microsoft Whiteboard? How to Open Microsoft Whiteboard With Search How to Open a Blank Whiteboard: With Click With Close By Default How to Open a Whiteboard Template: With the Templates Window With Preview With Menu How to Refresh a Whiteboard No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Microsoft Whiteboard? As a cloud-based or online app, Microsoft Whiteboard enables multiple users to collaborate on digital whiteboards in real time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a Log in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-a-log-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-a-log-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Create a Log in Notepad: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts With Code No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Create a Log in Notepad With Menu Step 1: First open a Notepad window. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Time/Date&amp;rdquo;. Notepad inserts the current time and date into the document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Notepad Keyboard Shortcuts (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/notepad-keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/notepad-keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;1. Menu Keyboard Shortcuts 2. File Menu Keyboard Shortcuts 3. Edit Menu Keyboard Shortcuts 4. Find and Replace Keyboard Shortcuts 5. View Menu Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorials slides:&#xA;See a video tutorial:&#xA;Menu Keyboard Shortcuts First open a Notepad window. On the keyboard, hold Alt and press one of the corresponding keys to open that menu. For example, press Alt + F to open the File menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set the Header/Footer in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-set-header-footer-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-set-header-footer-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;1. How to Remove the Header/Footer 2. How to Add the Header/Footer 3. What are the Header and Footer Codes? 4. How to Add Custom Words to the Header/Footer No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Remove the Header/Footer Step 1: First open a Notepad window. In the lower left click &amp;ldquo;More settings&amp;rdquo;. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Page setup&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Print Settings in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-print-settings-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-print-settings-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change Printing Orientation: With &amp;ldquo;Print&amp;rdquo; Menu With &amp;ldquo;More Settings&amp;rdquo; With &amp;ldquo;Page Setup&amp;rdquo; How to Change Color Settings: With &amp;ldquo;Print&amp;rdquo; Menu With &amp;ldquo;More Settings&amp;rdquo; How to Change Page Order How to Change Paper Source: With &amp;ldquo;Print&amp;rdquo; Menu With &amp;ldquo;Page Setup&amp;rdquo; How to Change Paper Media How to Change Paper Size How to Change Margins No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Print in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-print-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-print-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Print: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Exit the Print Window How to Add a Printer How to Change the Number of Copies How to Print to File How to Let Notepad Change Printing Preferences How to Print on Both Sides No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Print With Menu Step 1: First open a Notepad file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Save in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-save-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-save-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Save a File: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Save As: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Save Multiple Files: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Save a File With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Display of the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-notepad-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-notepad-display/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Font: With Menu With Settings How to Change the Reading Order How to Insert Unicode Control Characters How to Show Unicode Control Characters How to Apply Reconversion No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Change the Font With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Navigate the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Use &amp;ldquo;Go To&amp;rdquo;: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Clear the &amp;ldquo;Go To&amp;rdquo; Window How to Exit the &amp;ldquo;Go To&amp;rdquo; Window: With Click With Keyboard No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Use &#34;Go To&#34; With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Go to&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Search for Text in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-search-text-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-search-text-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Use Find: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Use Find Next: With Menu With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Use Find Previous: With Menu With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Apply Match Case How to Apply Wrap Around How to Clear the Find Bar How to Exit the Find Window: With Click With Keyboard How to Use Find and Replace: With Menu With Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Undo: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Redo With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Undo With Menu Step 1: First edit a Notepad file. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Undo&amp;rdquo;. Notepad reverses the last action. How to Undo With Right Click Step 1: Edit a Notepad file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-files-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-files-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Edit Text in Notepad How to Select Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Copy Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Cut Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Paste Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Delete Text in Notepad: With Menu With Right Click With Keyboard No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Microsoft Notepad App Settings (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-notepad-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-notepad-settings/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Choose How Files Are Opened How to Adjust When Notepad Starts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Choose How Files Are Opened Step 1: First open Notepad. In the upper right click the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; or gear button. Step 2: In the Settings window that opens, click the &amp;ldquo;Opening files&amp;rdquo; drop-down menu and select either &amp;ldquo;Open in a new tab&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Open in a new window&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Microsoft Notepad App Display (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-the-notepad-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-the-notepad-display/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Add/Remove the Status Bar How to Add/Remove Word Wrap With Menu With Settings How to Change the Notepad App Theme Color No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Add/Remove the Status Bar Step 1: First open Notepad. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;View&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Status bar&amp;rdquo; to toggle this option on or off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Zoom in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-zoom-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-zoom-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Zoom In: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Zoom Out: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Restore Default Zoom: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Zoom In With Menu Step 1: First open Notepad. In the upper left click the &amp;ldquo;View&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, hover over &amp;ldquo;Zoom&amp;rdquo;, and in the second menu that opens click &amp;ldquo;Zoom in&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Move Notepad: With Mouse With Right Click With Menu With a Tab How to Move a Tab: Outside a Window Into a Window No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Move Notepad With Mouse Step 1: First open Notepad. At the top of the window, click, hold, and drag the mouse to move the window. Release the mouse to stop moving the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Restore the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Restore Notepad: With Click With Double Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Restore Notepad With Click Step 1: First maximize Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Maximize&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window is restored to its original size. How to Restore Notepad With Double Click Step 1: Maximize Notepad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Maximize Notepad: With Click With Double Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a video:&#xA;How to Maximize Notepad With Click Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Maximize&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window maximizes. How to Maximize Notepad With Double Click Step 1: Open Notepad. Double click the top of the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Minimize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize Notepad: With Click With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Minimize Notepad With Click Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Minimize&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;-&amp;rdquo; button. The Notepad window minimizes. How to Minimize Notepad With Right Click Step 1: Open Notepad. Right click either the top or the upper left corner of the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize Notepad: With Mouse With Right Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Resize Notepad With Mouse Step 1: First open Notepad. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window, until the cursor becomes a double sided arrow. Step 2: Click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window. Release the mouse to stop resizing the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Close a Window: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts With Click With Right Click With Double Click With Hover With Hover and Right Click With Right Click on Taskbar How to Close All Windows With Menu How to Close a Tab: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut With Click With Right Click How to Close Tabs: On the Right Side Multiple Tabs No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open Files in the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-files-in-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-files-in-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a File: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open a Window: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut How to Open a Tab: With Menu With Keyboard Shortcut With Click With Right Click No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a File With Menu Step 1: First open Notepad. Go to the upper left and click &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin Notepad to the Taskbar: With Search With Right Click From Start How to Pin Notepad to Start No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Notepad to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;notepad&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Notepad App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notepad/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is Notepad? How to Open Notepad With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;What is Notepad? Notepad is a basic text editor that comes with Windows 11. This app creates text files for various applications, such as editing code or writing stories. Notepad can save files with UTF-8 encoding, and customize document headers and footers with special codes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Navigate the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Settings (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-navigate-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Switch Between Windows How to Cycle Forward Through All Windows How to Cycle Backwards Through All Windows How to Search For Sticky Notes How to Search for a Sticky Note Witih Click How to Clear the Search Bar How to Exit the Search Bar With Click How to Search for a Sticky Note With Keyboard Shortcut How to Clear the Search Bar With Keyboard Shortcut How to Move to a Word How to Move One Word to the Left How to Move One Word to the Right How to Move to the Start of a Line How to Move to the End of a Line How to Move to the Start of a Sticky Note How to Move to the End of a Sticky Note How to Move and Delete Words How to Delete the Previous Word How to Delete the Next Word No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Microsoft Sticky Notes App Settings (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-sticky-notes-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-sticky-notes-settings/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Enable Insights in a Sticky Note How to Turn &amp;ldquo;Confirm Before Deleting&amp;rdquo; Off: With Settings With Click No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial: See it in action with this video:&#xA;How to Enable Insights in a Sticky Note Step 1: First open the Notes List. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; or gear button. Step 2: In the Settings window that opens, click under the &amp;ldquo;Enable Insights&amp;rdquo; section to toggle this option on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Delete Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-delete-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-delete-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Delete a Sticky Note: With Menu With Click From the Notes List With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Delete a Sticky Note With Menu Step 1: First open a sticky note. Go to the upper right and click the &amp;ldquo;Menu&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; button. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Delete note&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Images in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-images-in-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-images-in-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Add an Image to a Sticky Note How to View an Image in a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Right Click How to Navigate the Image Viewer Window: How to Resize the Image Viewer Window How to Maximize and Restore the Image Viewer Window How to Close the Image Viewer Window How to Save an Image: With Menu With Right Click How to Open an Image in Photos How to Edit the Description of an Image How to Remove the Description of an Image How to Delete an Image: With Menu With Right Click No time to scroll down?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Undo and Redo in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-undo-redo-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Undo: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Redo: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Undo With Right Click Step 1: First edit a sticky note. Right click anywhere in the note. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Undo&amp;rdquo;. The previous action is reversed. How to Undo With Keyboard Shortcut Step 1: Edit a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Format Text in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-format-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Format Text: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Copy Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Cut Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut How to Paste Text: With Right Click With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Format Text With Click Method 1: First edit a sticky note and select any text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note How to Edit Text in a Sticky Note How to Select Text in a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Mouse With Keyboard With Keyboard Shortcut How to Delete Text in a Sticky Note No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;See a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Change the Color of a Sticky Note Step 1: First open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Sticky Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-create-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note: With Click With Right Click With Search With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Create a Sticky Note With Click Method 1: First open the Notes List. Go to the upper left corner and click the &amp;ldquo;New note&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; button. A new sticky note appears. Method 2: Open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Close the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-close-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Close the Notes List and Sticky Notes With Right Click How to Close the Notes List: With Click With Hover With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts How to Close a Sticky Note: With Click With Hover With Menu With Keyboard Shortcuts No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Close the Notes List and Sticky Notes With Right Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Theme Color of the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-change-sticky-notes-theme-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-change-sticky-notes-theme-color/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Change the Sticky Notes App Theme Color: With Start With the Notes List With Right Click No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Watch a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Change the Sticky Notes App Theme Color With Start Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click the Start (four blue squares) button. Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-move-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Mouse How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Move the Sticky Notes App Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. At the top of the window, click, hold, and drag to move the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Show All Notes in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-show-all-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-show-all-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Show All Notes: With Right Click With Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Show All Notes With Right Click Step 1: First minimize or hide all notes. Go down to the taskbar and right click the Sticky Notes app icon. Step 2: In the menu that opens, click &amp;ldquo;Show all notes&amp;rdquo;. The Notes List and all sticky notes display on the Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Restore the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-restore-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Restore the Notes List: With Double Click With Menu How to Restore a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Restore the Notes List With Double Click Step 1: First maximize the Notes List. Double click the top of the maximized Notes List. The Notes List is restored to its original size before being maximized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-maximize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Maximize the Notes List: With Menu With Double Click How to Maximize a Sticky Note: With Menu With Double Click No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Maximize the Notes List With Menu Step 1: First open the Notes List. Go down to the taskbar and hover the mouse over the Sticky Notes app icon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Minimize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-minimize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize a Sticky Note: With Click From the Notes List From the Notes List With Right Click With Menu How to Minimize the Notes List: With Click With Menu With Right Click With Start With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Minimize a Sticky Note With Click Step 1: First open the Notes List and open a sticky note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Resize the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-resize-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Menu No time to scroll down? Click through these presentation slides:&#xA;See a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Resize the Sticky Notes Window With Mouse Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. Hover the mouse over any edge or corner of the window. Step 2: After the cursor becomes a double sided arrow, click, hold, and drag the mouse to resize the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Notes List in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-notes-list/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List: With Search With Hover With Right Click From a Sticky Note With Keyboard Shortcut No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open the Notes List With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start menu that opens, click in the search bar at the top and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open a Sticky Note in the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-a-sticky-note/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note: With Double Click With Hover With Right Click From the Notes List No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;View a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Open a Sticky Note with Double Click Step 1: First open the Sticky Notes app. In the Notes List window, double click a sticky note to open it. How to Open a Sticky Note With Hover Step 1: Open the Sticky Notes app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Pin the Microsoft Sticky Notes App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-pin-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pin the Sticky Notes App: To the Taskbar With Search To the Taskbar With Right Click To the Taskbar From Start To Start No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Pin Sticky Notes to the Taskbar With Search Step 1: Go down to the taskbar and click Start (four blue squares). Step 2: In the Start window that opens, click the top search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sticky notes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-open-sticky-notes/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? How to Open the Microsoft Sticky Notes App With Search No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video here:&#xA;What is the Microsoft Sticky Notes App? Sticky Notes is a note-taking app that comes with Windows 11. Notes can have formatted text (bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, and bulleted lists), images, and recognized URLs. For further customization, choose from seven different colors of sticky notes and a &amp;ldquo;Dark&amp;rdquo; mode for the app.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
