<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customize Whiteboard on Quickly How Tutorials</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/customize-whiteboard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customize Whiteboard on Quickly How Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Quickly How Tutorials</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/customize-whiteboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Edit the Microsoft Whiteboard App Display (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-the-whiteboard-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-edit-the-whiteboard-display/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Pan Across the Canvas: With Click With Keyboard How to Change the Whiteboard Color How to Change the Whiteboard Background How to Enhance Inked Shapes No time to scroll down? Click through this tutorial presentation:&#xA;Follow along with a video tutorial:&#xA;How to Pan Across the Canvas With Mouse Step 1: First open a whiteboard template. Click, hold, and drag the mouse in any direction to pan across the canvas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Zoom In and Out of the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-zoom-in-and-out-of-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-zoom-in-and-out-of-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Zoom In: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut With Menu With Fit to Screen How to Center to Selection How to Zoom Out: With Click With Keyboard Shortcut With Menu With Fit to Screen No time to scroll down? Click through this presentation tutorial:&#xA;Watch a tutorial video:&#xA;How to Zoom In With Click Step 1: First open a whiteboard template. In the lower right side click the &amp;ldquo;Zoom in &amp;quot; button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Customize the Microsoft Whiteboard App (Windows 11)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-customize-microsoft-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-customize-microsoft-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial covers:&#xA;How to Minimize Whiteboard: With Click With Menu With Keyboard How to Maximize Whiteboard: With Click With Double Click With Menu With Keyboard How to Restore Whiteboard: With Click With Double Click With Menu With Keyboard How to Resize Whiteboard: With Mouse With Menu With Keyboard How to Move Whiteboard: With Mouse With Menu With Keyboard No time to scroll down? Click through these tutorial slides:&#xA;See a tutorial video:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
